soccerincollege.com 2017-06-25

# 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last reviewed on 02/29/2016
